Dracula is a drama, horror, tv movie film directed by Dan Curtis.
Dracula is searching for a woman who looks like his long dead wife.
Dracula, played by Jack Palance.
Arthur, played by Simon Ward.
Van Helsing, played by Nigel Davenport.
Lucy, played by Fiona Lewis.
Jonathan Harker, played by Murray Brown.
Mina, played by Penelope Horner.
Son of Dracula is a 1974 British musical film directed by Freddie
Francis and starring Harry Nilsson and Ringo Starr.
It was produced by Starr and released in 1974 by Apple Films.
It is also the title of a soundtrack released in conjunction with the film.
Keith Moon of The Who and John Bonham of Led Zeppelin both appear in the
film, alternating as the drummer in Count Downe's band.
Other band members include Klaus Voormann (another old friend of Starr), Peter Frampton, an uncredited
Leon Russell, and the regular Rolling Stones horn section of Bobby Keys and Jim Price.
In the film, Count Dracula is assassinated, and his son Count Downe is
supposed to inherit his control over the Netherworld.
Instead, the son wishes to become mortal and asks Dr.
Abraham Van Helsing to help him transform into an ordinary human.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
vampire, reincarnation, romance, gothic horror.
The tone is dark and emotional.